l'information
the information
une information importante
an important piece of information
des informations
some news
merci pour l'information
thanks for the information
une question
a question
une bonne question
a good question
une question difficile
a difficult question
pas de question
no question
la situation
the situation
une situation difficile
a difficult situation
une situation normale
a normal situation
la situation actuelle
the current situation
une solution
a solution
une solution simple
a simple solution
la bonne solution
the right solution
une solution possible
a possible solution
l'attention
attention
faites attention
be careful
beaucoup d'attention
a lot of attention
attention, s'il vous plaît
attention, please
l'université
the university
une grande université
a big university
une université française
a French university
à l'université
at the university
la qualité
quality
une bonne qualité
good quality
une qualité supérieure
superior quality
de bonne qualité
of good quality
une activité
an activity
une activité physique
a physical activity
des activités
some activities
une activité populaire
a popular activity
une possibilité
a possibility
une autre possibilité
another possibility
plusieurs possibilités
several possibilities
une réelle possibilité
a real possibility
la nation
the nation
une grande nation
a great nation
toute la nation
the whole nation
une nation moderne
a modern nation
la réalité
reality
la dure réalité
the harsh reality
en réalité
in reality
une autre réalité
another reality
la position
the position
une bonne position
a good position
ma position
my position
une position difficile
a difficult position
un problème
a problem
pas de problème
no problem
un petit problème
a small problem
un gros problème
a big problem
c'est important
it's important
très important
very important
une décision importante
an important decision
un message important
an important message
rapidement
quickly
très rapidement
very quickly
assez rapidement
quite quickly
répondez rapidement
answer quickly
exactement
exactly
c'est exact
that's right
exactement comme ça
exactly like that
pas exactement
not exactly